<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Adhi Yoga</title>
    <link>https://yogakarta.id/series/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Adhi Yoga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yogakarta.id/series/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>sohappytocyou - A Link Personalizer</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/sohappytocyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/sohappytocyou/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Sohappytocyou is a link personalizer that can personalize your favourite link, or personalize link that you want to share or recommend to your friend or audience.
Tech Stack I build this using Golang as the backend language and MySql as the database. This project not yet published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BalbalanCLI</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/balbalancli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/balbalancli/</guid>
      <description>Introduction BalbalanCLI is a simple CLI application that can show the latest football score and league standing.
Repository link here.
Getting Started Ensure that Go is installed in your computer.
Setup the API Key To get the API Key, please register to football-data.org. After getting the API Key or Token, then add your API Key through balbalancli config --token YOUR_API_KEY command.
Installation Run
go get -u github.com/yogamuris/balbalancli Usage Available league    Code League     PL English Premier League   PD Primera Division La Liga   SA Serie A   BL1 Bundesliga   FL1 Ligue One   DED Eredivisie   PPL Primeira Liga   CL UEFA Champions League    Available Command balbalancli [command] Available Commands: config Setting the BalbalanCLI Configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19 Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/cov19dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/cov19dashboard/</guid>
      <description>About this project This project is a website that display about COVID-19 cases in Indonesia.
This project can be access through this link.
Tech Stack I used Python as the backend language with Flask Framework. For the chart I used the highchart and CARTO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIVA App</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/sivaapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/sivaapp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction SIVA (Sistem Informasi Inventaris dan Akuntansi) adalah aplikasi yang dapat membantu pengguna dalam melakukan pencatatan keuangan dan inventaris. Aplikasi ini memiliki beberapa fitur, diantaranya:
 Pencatatan inventaris masuk dan keluar Manajemen stok Pencatatan invoice Pencatatan pemasukan dan pengeluaran Pencatatan hutang dan piutang  Tech Stack I used PHP as the backend with Laravel framework and MySQL as the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retinopathy Diabetic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/rdml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/rdml/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A website for retinopathy diabetic prediction. To predict the retinopathy diabetic occurence, I build the model using machine learning approach. The model that i was build, publised at this link.
This project can be access through this link.
Tech Stack Prediction model developed with Python and sklearn library. I used Python as the backend with Flask framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikin.pw - An URL Shortener</title>
      <link>https://yogakarta.id/projects/bikinpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yogakarta.id/projects/bikinpw/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bikinpw is an url shortener platform that can customizing your url into memorable url. This project available at github
Tech Stack I used Python as Backend and simple Javascript for frontend interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
